Aditya Prawira

Software Developer

A curious software developer with 1+ years of experience in a fast and dynamic development team environment. Aiming to apply proven skills and continuously learn new technology stack in improving human productivity through a piece of software.

Phone: 0402 555 502

Email: adityaprawira96@gmail.com Location: Melbourne, Australia **GitHub:** https://github.com/adit-prawira **Website:** https://adityaprawira.herokuapp.com **LinkedIn:** https://www.linkedin.com/in/aditya-prawira

WORK EXPERIENCES

Laputan Software, Melbourne — Software Developer

April 2022 - PRESENT

- Working with more than 5 technologies such as React, Redux-Saga, Typescript, GraphQL, Docker, and more.
- Develop serverless REST API and GraphQL with AWS lambda. Implement design patterns that improve the development process by 20%.

University of Melbourne, Melbourne — Mid-Level Full-stack Software Engineer

March 2022 - PRESENT

- Developed software for PeakHour Urban Technologies startup company and worked with more than 5 technologies such as Typescript, AWS, Docker, NestJS, React, etc.
- Data processing on large datasets to build server–side ML model with a performance 48.07% faster than expected. Deploy more than 4 features for both server–side and client–side.

Reesby, Melbourne — Front End Team Lead Intern

December 2021 - April 2022

- Selected as the top-performing intern 4 times by the technology team. Software testing for bugs and operating speed.
- Bugs fixing and documenting processes to increase efficiency by 18%.

Reesby, Melbourne — Front End Developer Intern

June 2021 - December 2021

- Developed a marketing tool that enables the organisation to reach a total of 24,786 clients for an organisation's event with one click of a button with React and Redux.
- Increase the delivery rate by 25% by developing a CI/CD pipeline from version control to AWS.

EDUCATIONS

RMIT University, Melbourne — Master of Engineering (Robotics and Mechatronics Engineering)

July 2020 - July 2022

- Final grade of GPA of 3.4 out of 4.
- Develop computer vision software and ML model for dairy cow action recognition as a final year project.

University of Melbourne, Melbourne — Bachelor of Science (Mechanical System)

July 2017 - July 2020

- A team of 4 developing a 3D CAD simulation for Warman Competition 2020 for the final year project. The final design is predicted to be in the top 5 by a professional engineer.

SKILLS

Database: PostgreSQL, PostGIS, MongoDB

Language: Typescript/Javascript, Python, Java, C++

Tech Stack: NodeJS, NestJS, Express, ReactJS, React Native, ReduxJS, Redux Toolkit, Jōtai, Docker, Kubernetes, AWS, CircleCI, GitlabCI, Jest, Material-UI, grommet, Rest API, GraphQL

PROJECTS

Face-Identity Computer Vision Project

November 2021 - December 2021

- Develop a human-computer interaction (HCI) face identification system backed by monolith API using Django, SQL, and AWS S3.
- (https://github.com/adit-prawira/face attendance server)
- Data acquisition with OpenCV and Google Voice Assistant integration for the voice user interface (VUI). Utilise multi-threading, and message queue to handle face recognition, voice assistant, and S3 events. (https://qithub.com/adit-prawira/face-attendance)

Kinesis Project

October 2021 - January 2022

- A fitness React native mobile app built with Typescript and backed with ExpressJS server, MongoDB Atlas, S3, and CircleCI. (https://github.com/adit-prawira/kinesis)

AWARDS

Team Member of the Month (09/2021) – Award for developing an automation software project used by the internal team for marketing purposes, reaching clients and meeting deadlines.

LANGUAGES

English (Fluent) and Indonesian (Native)